questions = [
    {
        'question' : 'What is the national flower of Bangladesh?',
        'options' : ['Water Lily', 'Rose', 'Lotus', 'Sunflower'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Water Lily'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which river is known as the lifeline of Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Padma River', 'Jamuna River', 'Meghna River', 'Bramaputra River'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Meghna River'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'What is the largest mangrove forest in Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Sundarbans', 'Lawachara National Park', 'Sathari National Park', 'Himchari National Park'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Sundarbans'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which city is known as the "City of Mosques" in Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Dhaka', 'Sylhet', 'Rajshahi', 'Bagerhat'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Bagerhat'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which year did Bangladesh gain independence from Pakistan?', 
        'options' : ['1990', '1970', '1971', '1973'],
        'correct_answer' : '1971'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Who is considered the national poet of Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Rabindranath Tagore', 'Kazi Nazrul Islam', 'Jasim Uddin', 'Shamsur Rahman'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Kazi Nazrul Islam'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which sport is the national game of Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Cricket', 'Football', 'Kabaddi', 'Hockey'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Kabaddi'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which Bangladeshi won the nobel peace price in 2006?', 
        'options' : ['Sheikh Mujibur Rahman', 'Sheikh Hasina', 'Dr. Muhammad Yunus', 'Khaleda Zia'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Dr. Muhammad Yunus'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'What is the currency of Bangladesh?', 
        'options' : ['Taka', 'Dollar', 'Euro', 'Dinner'],
        'correct_answer' : 'Taka'
    },
    {
        'question' : 'Which is the longest sea beach in the world?', 
        'options' : ['Patenga Beach', "Cox's Bazar Beach", 'Kuakata Beach', 'Inani Beach'],
        'correct_answer' : "Cox's Bazar Beach"
    }
]